cheat that he sent me
and it's got a list of a ton of things
can I just read off and ask questions
I think 30 million dollars a year in revenue
just off shopify apps
the Shopify ecosystem was interesting
I mean it's interesting
if you can create something really easily
and other people can copy you really easily
and then you don't control the payments
it's it was a whole wild experience in there
because shopify controls all the money
you don't you have to wait for your
your grandpa to give you your nickels
and they control the whole the whole thing
so we're like let's get the hell out of this world
but yeah we commerce looks like
535 Canadian which is what like 100 million American
no not that bad
yeah
like what's the conversion of monopoly money to USD